Everybody watches and acknowledges
you as the original founder.
Who is this?
Are you the Psycho Helmet?
Look at all these applause and
cheering you never had before.
How's that? It feels good, right?
No, not at all.
Let's meet face-to-face and talk.
I'm already by the base
of the broccoli.
It's not just broccoli anymore.
This thing has absorbed people's will and
turned into something entirely different.
Have you ever strongly
believed in something?
When strong will gathers, it can turn
something into reality in the world.
The world is about to
undergo a huge change.
A new God named Psycho Helmet
has come into existence
and descended.
God?
Aren't you just a manager
for your group?
I will put lore where Psycho Helmet
is the reincarnation of the creator god.
The one who guides people to the right path
and provide comfort to their heart.
Guide to the right path?
Do you really do that?
And comforting their hearts, too?
Dunno, I just made it up on the spot.
All they have to do is pray to the
Divine Tree 5 minutes a day.
That will be nourishment for me.
I leave the rest to their own
interpretation that they like.
I can see that you want
to complain about it,
but the followers are
having fun doing this.
Even Ritsu, even Reigen.
Oh, that one is an exception.
He realized pretty quick and tried
to get in the way of the festival.
Too bad, the winners are
the ones that had fun.
You also made Master Reigen say that.
Didn't you,
Dimple?
(MOB MOB WOW!)
I realized that our youth is grey
The origin of this uneasiness
Is yet unknown
Trains of emotions keep running
Through my brain
Struggling through this adolescence
Don't disturb my deep psyche
Who is that behind you?
Opposing ideas creates distortion
Exorcise all the sorrow
So, do what you can now
My life
Finally, break it down
(Want) Both greed
(Young) And honesty
(Burn) Are growing
(1) On this chest of mine
(Trance) I'm not waking up
(Chance) I want to wake up
(Stance) These two different faces of mine
(1) Are standing back-to-back
Taking things as it is
In this free relation where
We resent each other
Once these two become one
That smile becomes one
And only "1"
(MOB MOB WOW!)
"1"
One and only "1"
(MOB MOB WOW!)
"1"
One and only "1"
(Divine Tree 2 ~Peace~)
Don't be so grumpy.
Hanazawa is fine.
Anyway, come join the
Psycho Helmet Religion already.
We'll make it together
as the two leaders.
Why?
As far as I've seen, you've become
powerful enough on your own.
There's still room for growth
for you, Shigeo.
Think of your future. It would be
a waste to not use your powers.
I refuse.
Yeah, I knew you'd say that.
But your family, your friends,
every single person out there,
they all put their faith in
Lord Psycho Helmet
and are living in a happy world.
The only one who hasn't
in this city is just you, Shigeo.
They're not coming back from that.
How much longer
are you going to keep this act?
They're only brainwashed by you.
What about you?
When will you stop?
Are you angry?
I'm angry.
Of course I would.
Free them from their
brainwashing right now.
How did you even manage to brainwash
Ritsu and Master Reigen?
Phase one is touching the Divine Tree,
consuming part of the Divine Tree,
and other ways.
Physical contact allows me
to get in their head.
Phase two is by making the weaker-willed
get swallowed up by the herd mentality.
Reigen got caught by that.
You could say he's
swallowed up by the mood.
And now we're entering phase three.
The passion from the strong belief will
be transmitted to neighboring places.
It's only a matter of time
until the Psycho Helmet faith
spreads through the country.
And then it's going to be amazing.
I will really become a new God.
I don't really get it, but isn't becoming
a God really pointless?
Don't you understand
what you're doing?
Huh?
You're causing damage to the city.
Oh, the city?
Oops, didn't know about that.
Well, you can just
rebuild that again later.
Enough. Free everyone
from your brainwashing.
A one-sided sentimental argument.
That's not like you.
Besides, I didn't do anything
as bad as actual brainwashing.
I didn't overwrite their personality.
Their hobby, the things they like,
none of it were changed.
Ritsu, Reigen,
the Body Improvement Club,
none of their attitude to you changed.
It's just that now they're
Psycho Helmet's followers.
And not just that,
they would feel happy and share
their joy with one another.
Of course, I'm not saying
I'm leaving you out of all of this.
So? What are you complaining about?
What's wrong with what I'm doing?
What's wrong with that?
You're a coward, Dimple.
You're forcibly moving people's hearts
using your power so they can't resist.
You're just doing as you please.
The world always has laws and societal
structures that make people can't resist.
As long as you don't pay them any mind,
there won't be any problem.
Besides, if I don't comply to you,
you're planning to use force
as a last resort, right?
I have no other choice.
Because you brainwashed
my family and friends.
Even now, I'm actually
holding back quite a lot.
Wait a sec, Kageyama.
What Dimple is trying
to do isn't that bad.
Huh?
Calm down for a sec.
It's bad if you resort to violence
just because you can't comprehend it.
No, I can still make it.
The Psycho Helmet Religion
hasn't fully begun.
No, if you lay a hand,
it'll be over.
Your relationship with Dimple, that is.
Even our relationship will also end.
If you plan to demolish the
Psycho Helmet Religion with brute force,
then I will stop you.
Even if you manage to defeat me,
your brother and Reigen
won't let it slide.
Everyone in the city
will stand to oppose you.
Dimple, you...
Hanazawa doesn't wish you any harm.
He's speaking from his heart
to convince you, for your own sake.
I told you, if you leave them be,
their daily life will still...
Come out in your true body, Dimple.
I want to talk face-to-face.
Stop it, Kageyama!
We've been talking all this time,
haven't we?
If you're going to hurt
the Psycho Helmet Religion...
If you're going to hurt the Divine Tree,
then you must face me!
Come to your senses, Hanazawa!
Unfortunately, Hanazawa is
already in his right mind.
I just have one extra thing
that is important to me now.
Until you give it up and go home,
I will fight back!
Sorry.
Dimple, come out!
Divinity dwells inside
those who believe.
Right now, there is a God in Hanazawa.
My power is overflowing...
Hana...zawa...!
Sorry.
Oh no, I damaged the Divine Tree again.
Good job, Hanazawa.
Shigeo, cool down a bit under
the wrappings of the Divine Tree's roots.
You'll change your way of thinking.
That was really strong.
The broccoli roots?
These roots are dangerous.
Get out of here, Hanazawa!
Huh?
Are you serious now, Kageyama?!
Lord Psycho Helmet, get behind me!
A-amazing!
I knew it, you really are amazing!
Oh no, you opened an air hole
on the Divine Tree.
Oh well, it'll immediately get closed.
Now that I've become a God,
you can't deal with me
by ordinary means, Shigeo.
It's useless.
Dimple, why?
Why won't you show yourself?
Are you...
Are you afraid of me?
Are we still doing this?
Enough.
Enough already.
Don't make me feel this way.
Don't you get it, Dimple?
Come out already.
Otherwise...
My power...
They're being drained away?
Correct.
You realized that a bit too late.
You carelessly walked in here when
I asked you to. That was a mistake.
But your biggest mistake...
...is opposing me!
Dimple, what is the meaning of this?!
I told you, calm down.
If I can't convince you,
then maybe that girl can.
If Tsubomi tries to convince you,
maybe you'll calm down
for a bit, eh?
Mob, you can't cause trouble
for the Psycho Helmet Religion!
Get a hint already.
How's that?
Hey now.
You always get so serious
when it comes to Tsubomi.
Let me make this clear now.
Shigeo, that girl is way
out of your league.
What?
Tsubomi Takane is the type of person that
will flatly refuse things she doesn't want.
When I tried to somewhat forcefully
hand the candy, she'd slap them away.
Even when persuaded by her friends,
she still doesn't show any interest.
She's a strong woman that lives
following her own values,
never affected by others.
No wonder she's not interested when
you bragged about your psychic powers.
Even if you trained your body,
she still won't need you, Shigeo.
However,
right now she is a member
of the Psycho Helmet Religion.
In other words, she might actually
fall for you if you become the founder.
That is stupid.
Here I thought I drained
most of your strength.
Seems like you still have
some left in you.
Maybe it's still too soon for me
to appear in my real body?
Eh, whatever.
Right now, I won't lose to even you.
Hey! Hold on!
You're getting cocky here,
goddammit!
Don't get arrogant
just because I'm playing nice!
Seems like I have to get serious, too!
Take a good look.
Behold, this is the joyous birth of...
God Dimple!
So what?
Here I come!
God Punch!
God Dash!
And then!
God Slam!
How does a God's power feel?
Are you giving up?
God Toss!
God...!
Sandbag!
God Straight!
I know you, Shigeo.
This isn't enough to defeat you.
But he should be at his limit soon.
I can feel his enormous strength that
has been absorbed through the tree.
I saw the limit of his energy
in the battle with the Claw's boss.
It's not unlimited.
It will actually run out.
He was also losing to
Keiji Mogami's mental attack.
He's not invincible.
I know best how to beat
Shigeo Kageyama...
-That is your true form?
-Huh?
Is that supposed to be who you are?
You must be joking.
You still have an impudent mouth
even after all that beating.
I'll make you regret
not joining my side!
-Is that really what you're thinking?
-What?
If that is so, you shouldn't
have pulled your punches.
Your power, your actions,
even your words.
They're all fakes.
Don't try to fool me into
thinking that's the real you.
This facade of yours...
They don't fit you. I won't allow it.
I won't acknowledge it.
Who the heck do you think you are?!
You won't acknowledge me?!
Don't you so easily deny...
...the thing that I've always wished for!
God Beam!
Oh no, I put too much energy into it!
Shigeo!
I-I can feel his anger!
H-hang on...
That brat. How come he still
have this much power left?
I have to kill him before he kills me!
That surprised me.
I thought I was going to die.
A little bit more,
and I would've lost faith in you.
Oh crap, I'm getting scared
just from his glare.
I just want to know
what you're really thinking.
Say something, Dimple.
What do you mean,
"What I'm really thinking?"
I've always been using you all along.
It never changed.
I'm sad.
Is this where we say our goodbyes?
Is he going to attack?!
Full spiritual power!
Let's finish this!
Your shirt is so lame!
The blue light shined
Dazzling my eye at 01:30 AM
Even as I swiped the page over,
The smiles of friends besides me remain
Yes, I want someone to understand
All the colorless and transparent wishes
All the breath stuck within
The depth of my heart
Suddenly flowed out
Bringing my consciousness back
I remember the days hung dry
The very normal days passed by
Even if reality is corrupted
The sky we saw together
Was definitely real
It's harder to understand than
The grammar on the blackboard
The story that disappears
Under 24 hours makes me sad and lonely
It's so hard, and I find myself
On the verge of giving up again and again
But I...
The current me will no longer give up
Overflowing emotions on my sleeve,
Running through worry and doubt
Nobody has decided
if the future is 0 or 100,
So I'll paint over them myself
Even if my existence itself
can't be proven,
If this world struck me in my heart
I will flood it with cobalt blue
Man, there are so many things
I can't empathize with you, Shigeo.
You could've used your psychic powers
to get more in your life.
Really, you're just so annoying.
Next on episode six of
Mob Psycho 100 III,
"Divine Tree 3 ~Dimple is~"